kicksocca.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy - Kick Socca - Kick Socca

## Introduction

This privacy statement covers the site www.kicksocca.com. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us.

Shainaz Media Inc takes your privacy seriously and takes every reasonable precaution to safeguard the personal information you supply to it.

Shainaz Media Inc. recognizes that your privacy and the protection of your personal information is important to you, this statement discloses how Shainaz Media Inc. helps to protect your personal information while using the Shainaz Media Inc. Web Site www.kicksocca.com

## Collection of your personal information

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and choose a password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site.

Once you register with Shainaz Media Inc. you will receive a welcome email, and a weekly newsletter.

Shainaz Media Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on www.kicksocca.com.

Shainaz Media Inc. collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

Shainaz Media Inc. collects demographic (information about you, such as name, age and address) and lifestyle (information about your interests and purchasing habits). Shainaz Media Inc. collects data about you, including answers to specific questions asked by Shainaz Media Inc. sponsors.

This information is used to assist Shainaz Media Inc. and third parties in sending you by, email, sms, voice, post or other appropriate means, communications about their products and services.

## Use of your personal information

Shainaz Media Inc. will not use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described within this Privacy Statement and within the registration opt-in statement without your prior consent. The following statement is prominently displayed before you can join Shainaz Media Inc.

“By registering and entering your details you consent to Shainaz Media Inc. and its clients sending you information about products and/or services that may be of interest to you.You also agree to the terms and conditions of the privacy statement that govern how your information will be processed.”

Sponsors of the Shainaz Media Inc. questionnaires have their own privacy policies and some have their own opt-in statements, Shainaz Media Inc. strongly recommends that you read and understand this information.

Your data together with that of other subscribers to Shainaz Media Inc. may be aggregated at Postcode or other levels for the building of statistical and analytical tables. At no time will your data be individually identifiable in such tables.

## General disclosure of personal information

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

Personally identifiable information – We Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties, we share the information that you have answered within the questionnaires with the relevant client. The clients use this to profile you, this enables them to send you targeted communications.

Once you register with Shainaz Media Inc. you consent to Shainaz Media Inc. and it’s clients being able to send you relevant communications.

The collection of data by Shainaz Media Inc. through registration on third party sites may lead to your data also being held by that third party site.

The data that you provide to Shainaz Media Inc., is held by both Shainaz Media Inc. and the sponsors, of the questionnaires that you answer. Shainaz Media Inc. holds your data in a central database and this database is only accessed by reference to interest or demographic categories in order to provide you with information about those interests you have selected. The process of supplying you with this information is at all times under the control of Shainaz Media Inc. although specialist third party suppliers may carry out the dispatch.

## Sponsored Questionnaires and Co-branded sites

Every user must agree and opt-in to the following statement before completing their Shainaz Media Inc. registration:

“By registering and entering your details you consent to Shainaz Media Inc. and its clients sending you information about products and/or services that may be of interest to you. You also agree to the terms and conditions of the privacy policy that govern how your information will be processed.”

Each questionnaires on Shainaz Media Inc. is sponsored by a client, by giving a positive response and entering the questionnaire on Shainaz Media Inc. you are giving your consent for the sponsor / client sending you information about products and/or services that may be of interest to you. You will also have the opportunity to say “not applicable” to a sponsors questions on Shainaz Media Inc.The information you provide may be used, by Shainaz Media Inc. and its Clients, to provide you with information and offers by post. If you would prefer not to receive such offers please indicate your preference by ticking the box provided, located on the Amend Details page.

At times it may be appropriate for Shainaz Media Inc., its clients or sponsors to contact you with offers and information in respect of your interests or to inform you about subjects upon which you have requested information through your mobile phone or other PDA devices. Before doing so Shainaz Media Inc. will always ask you for your specific consent. If having given consent previously, you wish to withdraw this consent you may do so by logging on and amending your details on the site.

Your data may be provided to clients of Shainaz Media Inc. to be appended to information they already hold about you for the purpose of contacting you with information about their products and services. When first contacting you these clients will seek your appropriate consent.

Shainaz Media Inc. may from time to time use third party suppliers to provide all or part of a service to you. Shainaz Media Inc. shall only be entitled to supply such of your personal information as is necessary to enable them to provide the relevant service to you.

You should be aware that such outside service providers might be based in countries outside the European Union whose laws provide for a different standard of protection for your personal data than that provided under English law. In such circumstance Shainaz Media Inc. will have in place contractual arrangements which will require your data to be processed at least to a standard compliant with the Data Protection Act 1988.

Except as provided above, Shainaz Media Inc. will not provide your personal information to any third party without your prior consent, however, under certain circumstances the force of law may require the provision of information to the legal authorities. In order to maintain the integrity of its website and safeguard the interests of its subscribers Shainaz Media Inc. will comply with any such legally binding request.

## Managing your personal information

The data you provide to Shainaz Media Inc. will be held as you have provided it. You may at any time amend or update your data by contacting us.

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us.

We are entitled by law to charge a maximum fee of $10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## Deregistration and un-subscribing from emails

You may at any time deregister from Shainaz Media Inc. by contacting us.

There is information on how you can un-subscribe at the bottom of every email that Shainaz Media Inc. send out ether on behalf of Shainaz Media Inc. or its clients and sponsors.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

## Security and storage of your personal information

The Internet is not a 100% secure medium for communication and, accordingly, Shainaz Media Inc. cannot guarantee the security of any information you send to Shainaz Media Inc. via the Internet. Shainaz Media Inc. is not responsible for any loss or damage you or others may suffer as a result of the loss of confidentiality of such information.

Shainaz Media Inc. is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities.

You must type the correct password to access your Shainaz Media Inc. account information. It is your responsibility to ensure the security of your Shainaz Media Inc. password and not to reveal this information to others.

Personal information collected by Shainaz Media Inc. may be stored and processed outside the Canada. By using Shainaz Media Inc., you consent to any such transfer of information outside of the Canada.

## Use of Cookies

A cookie is a very small text file that a Web site saves to your computer’s hard disk to store information that you provide about yourself or to store your preferences.

Shainaz Media Inc. uses cookies whenever you login to Shainaz Media Inc. Shainaz Media Inc. stores your unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from page to page at the site without having to login in again on each page. Shainaz Media Inc. uses session cookies to store data on our server that are individually identifiable when you log out of Shainaz Media Inc., these session cookies are deleted from your computer.

Shainaz Media Inc. also uses cookies to improve the experience. For example, Shainaz Media Inc. may store your login details in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you log out. This cookie allows you to be automatically logged in the next time you visit Shainaz Media Inc. If you are using a public computer or do not otherwise want this information to be stored, you can un-check the “remember me” tick box when you log-in or register, and this cookie will not be used.

The sites or services you visited may store their own cookies on your computer. Shainaz Media Inc. recommends that you read each site’s privacy statement to understand their policies and practices regarding the use of cookies. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using the settings on your browser. If you have cookies disabled in your browser you are still able to use the Shainaz Media Inc. site but you will not have the benefit of an automatic login.

The functionality of Shainaz Media Inc. depends upon your browser accepting session cookies. Shainaz Media Inc. tracks visitors to and on the Shainaz Media Inc. site by using referrer tracking. Shainaz Media Inc. uses click thru and open mail tracking when sending emails. This process allows Shainaz Media Inc. and its clients the ability to profile the recipients of their communications.

Or our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

On this website we use Google Analytics to measure and analyse information with respect to visits to our website. To that effect we use your IP address to collect, among other things, internet traffic data and data regarding your browser type and computer.

In addition cookies are used. A cookie is a small file that is stored on your computer when you visit a website. If you visit the website again, it is recognized as a repeat visit by means of the cookie. The cookie contains merely a unique number and therefore no personal data. The cookie cannot be used to identify you on websites of third parties, including Nedstat.

It is possible to configure your web browser to refuse cookies or to be informed if a cookie is set. We refer to the manual of your web browser. We will not use the IP addresses or cookies to identify you personally.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.kicksocca.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

Shainaz Media Inc. will occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top and bottom of the Privacy Statement. AS Media Inc. will obtain your opt-in consent for any updates to this Privacy Statement that materially expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Statement at the time of collection.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Shainaz Media Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database.

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement, please Contact us.

* * *
